LEE JAE-IN, KIM WOO-SEOK, CHOI YE-BIN
CHA WOO-MIN, AN JI-HO, JUNG SO-RI
SCRIPTWRITER: KANG MIN-JI
DIRECTOR: IM DAE-WOONG
NIGHT HAS COME
ALL PEOPLE, ORGANIZATIONS, LOCATIONS,
AND INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS.
Get your phones!
It's not mine.
Na-hee!
I found it!
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
-Do you have your phone?
-No.
-What about you?
-Not yet.
Are you okay?
Where is it?
What now?
Get your phone.
I got mine.
Let's hurry up and find hers.
For breaking the rules,
Oh Hye-seung will be executed.
Oh Hye-seung was a Citizen.
PARTICIPANTS MUST VOTE AND
IDENTIFY THE MAFIA.
VOTE NOW.
For breaking the rules,
Kang Ye-won will be executed.
WELCOME TO MURYEONG RETREAT CENTER.
Kang Ye-won was...
-...a Mafia.
-Guys, hurry!
You must vote!
Vote or you die!
Who should we vote to kill?
Who?
For breaking the rules,
Lee Hyun-jun and Park Jung-eun
will be executed.
were Citizens.
I found it!
-You got it?
-Yes.
Vote first.
I'll keep looking.
What?
-Screw it.
-I got it.
Hyun-ho!
Your phone.
-Give it to me.
-Get lost, punk.
Darn you!
That scumbag.
For breaking the rules,
Kim Yeon-ju will be executed.
Kim Yeon-ju was a Citizen.
WILL YOU VOTE FOR BAEK EUN-HA?
Kim So-mi voted for Baek Eun-ha.
Baek Eun-ha?
Baek Eun-ha voted for Kim So-mi.
Park Woo-ram voted for...
-...Baek Eun-ha.
-Darn it.
Choi Mi-na voted for Baek Eun-ha.
-Shin Seung-bin...
-No, I didn't.
...voted for Baek Eun-ha.
-Kim Jin-ha...
-I didn't.
...voted for Baek Eun-ha.
Ahn Na-hee voted for Baek Eun-ha.
Hyun-ho!
Hyun-ho, I'll do it.
Jun-hee, your phone.
Hurry up and vote.
Hurry.
What about the others?
We must find Yoon-seo's too.
I'll look so you just vote already!
Cha Yu-jun voted for Baek Eun-ha.
You must vote fast.
There's no time.
It's Baek Eun-ha.
Don't vote and we die.
If we vote for her too, she'll die.
What else do you want to do?
We'll scatter the votes.
So we all get one vote.
Vote for each other.
Kim Jun-hee.
We'll vote for each other, okay?
-Jin Da-beom...
-Be quick.
voted for Oh Jung Won.
Oh Jung-won voted for Jin Da-beom.
Lee Yoon-seo voted for Kim Jun-hee.
Kim Jun-hee voted for Lee Yoon-seo.
Im Eun-chan voted for Nam Yeon-woo.
Nam Yeon-woo voted for Im Eun-chan.
For breaking the rules,
-Jang Hyun-ho will be executed.
-Hurry up.
Hyun-ho!
Jang Hyun-ho was a Citizen.
WELCOME TO MURYEONG RETREAT CENTER.
Voting is over.
With ten votes, Baek Eun-ha...
...got the most, and she will be executed.
Baek Eun-ha was a Citizen.
I said I was a Citizen.
I said it wasn't me!
I said it wasn't me.
Why vote for me?
Why?
Why me?
ASSEMBLY HALL
Night has come.
EPISODE 4
Ju-young.
Ju...
Hey.
Ju-young.
Lee Ju-young.
-What is it?
-Ju-young's weird.
Why?
During the night, Lee Ju-young...
...was executed by the Mafia.
Lee Ju-young...
-...was a Citizen.
-Ju-young!
Before the last vote closed,
the Doctor nominated who to Heal.
They nominated Cha Yu-jun.
I don't know.
-Morning has come.
-Ju-young.
All participants, identify the Mafia...
...and begin to vote.
I think she was strangled with this.
I said I wouldn't hand in my phone.
I said I didn't want to!
If we hadn't turned in our phones,
we wouldn't have slept here.
And they wouldn't have died.
You killed them all, Jun-hee.
-It's on you!
-Stop it.
If only we'd voted sooner.
Then they wouldn't have died.
They're not wrong.
We survived by pure luck.
You and Go Kyung-jun,
what'll you do about it now?
Did I suggest we hand them in?
Kim Jun-hee you scumbag,
you said we just had to give up our phones!
This happened because of you.
It's on you.
I'm sorry.
The game must take place
within the boundaries.
Whatever.
The class president got us into this.
Let's vote for him today.
You said it was a good idea...
...and took everyone's phones.
Why change your tune now?
You looked pretty relaxed last night.
Why did you take your phone in secret?
You're the most suspicious here.
Hey.
Isn't it obvious?
How are we to trust Jun-hee?
He could be part of the Mafia.
JIN DA-BEOM
Guys!
Our lives depend on this game.
Why entrust someone else with mine?
I just used my brain.
If not,
I could've died.
Hey.
Stop it.
Please.
Do you want to fight in this situation?
How long must we fight
over a game that kills?
Won't you go home?
How can we go home?
We can't leave.
The Mafia Game.
If we figure out...
...who started it and why,
we can find a way out.
Then we can all get out without
anyone else dying.
We'll figure out a way later.
Let's move the others.
Move what?
We can't leave them like this.
We must move them to the freezer.
Hey, Go Kyung-jun.
Let go, psycho.
Don't leave.
Stay and help.
If we do it, we do it together.
You're being cheap...
...and sneaking away again?
What did you say?
I shouldn't have collected the phones.
It wasn't your fault.
We didn't know about that rule.
No.
It's all my fault.
Kim Jun-hee.
Until the game's actually over,
people will keep dying.
If you really want to be responsible,
think of how to find a way to
get everyone out safely.
Okay?
Okay.
FROZEN HAIRTAIL
MAIN MENU
Yoon-seo.
-Yoon-seo.
What's wrong?
Yoon-seo.
Are you okay?
Hey.
-Breathe.
-Are you okay?
Breathe, Yoon-seo.
Slowly.
It's okay.
Are you all right?
Yoon-seo.
LEE YOON-SEO
Are you okay?
What happened?
You don't remember.
You passed out.
I was so scared.
I'm fine.
Let me wrap the bandage for you.
Why do they have to die?
Na-hee.
Hyun-ho was trying to help me.
Why do we have to suffer like this?
Just turn yourself in.
If you're part of the Mafia, tell me.
Do you think they would if it were you?
Darn it.
Let me try again.
Who's certain someone's part of the Mafia?
Reveal yourself if you're the Police then.
Police!
Are you not going to reveal yourself?
I don't think they would do it either.
They won't.
Why the heck won't you cooperate?
Hey, Class President.
It's you, isn't it?
The Citizens died because you didn't
allow us to vote.
Wasn't it the Mafias' plan to
kill all the Citizens?
What are you talking about?
Did you not read the notice?
It wasn't just Citizens.
A Mafia died too.
We can be almost sure about
the Doctor though.
It's not me.
It's not me either.
It's you two.
Who would save Yu-jun other than you guys?
I don't know why the Doctor
saved me either.
But it's really not me.
BAEK EUN-HA: 10 VOTES,
IM EUN-CHAN: 1 VOTE,
OH JUNG-WON: 1 VOTE, JIN DA-BEOM: 1 VOTE
Hey, So-mi.
Eun-ha said you were a Mafia yesterday.
Did you pick her because she caught you?
Hey, I...
I voted for her...
...because she was going to
vote for me first.
What about you?
You're a Mafia, aren't you?
I'm not.
Ju-young...
...and you had a big argument yesterday.
We had an argument,
but why would I kill her because of it?
You lick her boots in front of her,
but you badmouth her that she's a
jerk behind her back.
I guess you wanted to kill her.
No.
No wonder.
Ju-young did treat Min-ha like a maid.
That's really not true!
Darn it, you talk so much.
Turn yourself in, or you'll see blood.
Go Kyung-jun.
Why did you do that?
What the heck are you talking about?
Why were you hiding your phone yesterday?
You knew they would die if we don't vote.
You didn't tell us on purpose
so that they all die.
I told you.
How can we trust that punk?
If you didn't believe it,
why did you force us to do it?
It's you who killed Ju-young, you punk.
Do you think I don't know that?
What?
You told her how you felt about her,
but she rejected you.
And it got spread online...
...only for you to get bashed.
-I was just joking.
-Don't try to fool me, idiot!
You kneeled and begged her...
...to delete the post.
Everyone here knows that.
Choi Mi-na.
Say something.
You took the video.
Yes.
It has nothing to do with this.
It has everything to do with this...
...because you're a darn Mafia!
You talked behind her back and
called her a fox.
You killed Ju-won first...
...because it would've been obvious...
...if you had killed Ju-young first,
didn't you?
No.
How can I be a Mafia?
It's you.
Screw it.
Darn it.
Go Kyung-jun voted for Park Woo-ram.
GO KYUNG-JUN VOTED FOR PARK WOO-RAM.
No, I'm not.
Don't vote for me.
I can tell from his eyes.
He's 100-percent Mafia.
Hey.
(WILL YOU VOTE FOR PARK WOO-RAM?)
(SHIN SEUNG-BIN VOTED FOR PARK WOO-RAM.)
Shin Seung-bin and Kim Jin-ha...
...voted for Park Woo-ram.
You jerks.
Hey.
You punks should vote for him too.
Choi Mi-na.
He holds so many grudges against you too.
Since Ju-young is dead, it's your turn.
Hey.
Go Kyung-jun.
Get out of my way.
How dare that piece of
trash try to kill me?
But...
...they won't switch the
target and accuse us, will they?
What are you talking about?
There are 15 of us.
The three of us voted for Woo-ram,
but there are a lot more
people who didn't vote yet.
Darn it.
Should we get some insurance?
Where are you going?
Hey.
Guys.
Where are you guys going?
Hey!
Hold on.
We should talk before you go.
We can meet again after a break.
What?
WILL YOU VOTE FOR PARK WOO-RAM?
Choi Mi-na voted for Park Woo-ram.
Choi Mi-na!
Why did you do that?
What?
Come to think of it, Kyung-jun has a point.
I knew it.
I had a bad feeling...
...when I saw his eyes looking
at Ju-young yesterday.
-What?
-This crazy witch.
Woo-ram.
Don't. I'll persuade them.
Aren't you hungry?
Ji-soo.
ROOM 302
You're not really a Doctor, are you?
Because I'm not.
I know.
I believe you.
-But who on earth...
-I'm really not.
-Please trust me.
-Yu-jun.
I'm so confused right now.
What's going on?
What happened?
I fell prey to Kyung-jun's plot.
I shouldn't have let them vote.
Do you think they would've listened...
...if you had stopped them?
Instead of talking here,
don't we have to go...
...and tell the other guys to
vote for someone else?
Who should we ask them to vote for?
How would I know?
Anyway,
it'll be fine as long as it's not us.
If we only know who the Mafias are.
SWIMMING POOL CAFETERIA
If you don't vote for Woo-ram,
do you think those punks will save you?
They will do anything to save themselves.
Understand?
Everyone voted for Eun-ha.
Woo-ram and So-mi are behind it.
You should get revenge.
We should team up.
You can use the cafeteria too.
How nice is that?
Right?
Woo-ram has to be a Mafia.
He got all worked up...
...because he has so many dirty secrets.
Eat.
Hurry up and eat.
The noodles will get soggy.
IM EUN-CHAN, NAM YEON-WOO,
AND JIN DA-BEOM VOTED FOR PARK WOO-RAM.
What's this?
-Why did they do this?
-These jerks...
How can they do this to me?
Right.
Ji-soo and Yu-jun are on our side.
It'll be fine.
I'll find a way.
Okay?
A way?
Screw it.
I have no choice.
It's me or Kyung-jun.
It will not end before one of us dies.
Don't you think so?
Let's do the same thing he does.
Let's vote for Kyung-jun.
What?
He always bullies others.
That scumbag deserves to die.
That jerk...
...will do anything to survive.
Yes.
Let's say he kills me today.
What will happen tomorrow then?
Who do you think he's going to
vote for tomorrow?
It'll be one of you.
Is it me or Kyung-jun?
Make a choice.
Woo-ram is right.
I'll vote for Kyung-jun.
Me too.
I saw what he did until today.
We should stop him.
I'll vote for him too.
Guys.
If you don't help me, I'll die.
You know it.
Are you going to kill me?
Please.
Please help me.
KIM JUN-HEE VOTED FOR GO KYUNG-JUN.
KIM SO-MI VOTED FOR GO KYUNG-JUN.
PARK WOO-RAM VOTED FOR GO KYUNG-JUN.
WILL YOU VOTE FOR GO KYUNG-JUN?
PARK WOO-RAM, LEE YOON-SEO,
AHN NA-HEE, KIM SO-MI,
KIM JUN-HEE, AND OH JUNG-WON
VOTED FOR GO KYUNG-JUN.
Look.
I knew it.
That crazy jerk must have a death wish.
Only Yu-jun and Ji-soo are left, right?
Yes.
They should be in their room.
Their room?
You guys aren't feeling well.
Get some rest.
I'll go with them.
Do you want to go to the infirmary?
It's a little scary here.
Okay.
Do you want to go in?
We don't even know what this is.
That's why I should go.
I'll be back quickly.
Yoon-seo.
Be careful.
I will.
Yoon-seo!
-Yoon-seo.
-Are you okay?
Yoon-seo!
NIGHT HAS COME
THIS CONTENT WAS PRODUCED THROUGH...
GWANGJU INFORMATION AND CONTENT AGENCY'S...
2022 OTT PLATFORM CONTENT
PRODUCTION BUSINESS.
Ripped and resynced by YoungJedi